i abstract: Control the typesetting of the abstract environment
i acro: Typeset acronyms
i amscls: AMS document classes for LaTeX
i amsfonts: TeX fonts from the American Mathematical Society
i amsmath: AMS mathematical facilities for LaTeX
i arydshln: Draw dash-lines in array/tabular
i atbegshi: Execute stuff at \shipout time
i atveryend: Hooks at the very end of a document
i auxhook: Hooks for auxiliary files
i babel: Multilingual support for LaTeX, LuaLaTeX, XeLaTeX, and Plain TeX
i babel-french: Babel contributed support for French
i beamer: A LaTeX class for producing presentations and slides
i biber: A BibTeX replacement for users of BibLaTeX
i biber.windows: windows files of biber
i biber.x86_64-linux: x86_64-linux files of biber
i biblatex: Sophisticated Bibliographies in LaTeX
i biblatex-apa: BibLaTeX citation and reference style for APA
i biblatex-chicago: Chicago style files for BibLaTeX
i biblatex-ieee: IEEE style files for BibLaTeX
i biblatex-nature: BibLaTeX support for Nature
i biblatex-publist: BibLaTeX bibliography support for publication lists
i biblatex-vancouver: Vancouver style for BibLaTeX
i bibtex: Process bibliographies (bib files) for LaTeX or other formats
i bibtex.windows: windows files of bibtex
i bibtex.x86_64-linux: x86_64-linux files of bibtex
i bigintcalc: Integer calculations on very large numbers
i bitset: Handle bit-vector datatype
i booktabs: Publication quality tables in LaTeX
i caption: Customising captions in floating environments
i carlisle: David Carlisle's small packages
i chktex: Check for errors in LaTeX documents
i chktex.windows: windows files of chktex
i chktex.x86_64-linux: x86_64-linux files of chktex
i cm: Computer Modern fonts
i colortbl: Add colour to LaTeX tables
i csquotes: Context sensitive quotation facilities
i ctablestack: Catcode table stable support
i dehyph: German hyphenation patterns for traditional orthography
i dvipdfmx: An extended version of dvipdfm
i dvipdfmx.windows: windows files of dvipdfmx
i dvipdfmx.x86_64-linux: x86_64-linux files of dvipdfmx
i dvips: A DVI to PostScript driver
i dvips.windows: windows files of dvips
i dvips.x86_64-linux: x86_64-linux files of dvips
i ec: Computer modern fonts in T1 and TS1 encodings
i enumitem: Control layout of itemize, enumerate, description
i epstopdf-pkg: Call epstopdf "on the fly"
i eso-pic: Add picture commands (or backgrounds) to every page
i etaremune: Reverse-counting enumerate environment
i etex: An extended version of TeX, from the NTS project
i etexcmds: Avoid name clashes with e-TeX commands
i etoolbox: e-TeX tools for LaTeX
i euenc: Unicode font encoding definitions for XeTeX
i everyshi: Take action at every \shipout
i fancyhdr: Extensive control of page headers and footers in LaTeX2e
i fancyvrb: Sophisticated verbatim text
i filecontents: Create an external file from within a LaTeX document
i filehook: Hooks for input files
i firstaid: First aid for external LaTeX files and packages that need updating
i float: Improved interface for floating objects
i fontawesome5: Font Awesome 5 with LaTeX support
i fontaxes: Additional font axes for LaTeX
i fontspec: Advanced font selection in XeLaTeX and LuaLaTeX
i fp: Fixed point arithmetic
i framed: Framed or shaded regions that can break across pages
i geometry: Flexible and complete interface to document dimensions
i gettitlestring: Clean up title references
i glyphlist: Adobe Glyph List and TeX extensions
i graphics: The LaTeX standard graphics bundle
i graphics-cfg: Sample configuration files for LaTeX color and graphics
i graphics-def: Colour and graphics option files
i grfext: Manipulate the graphics package's list of extensions
i grffile: Extended file name support for graphics (legacy package)
i helvetic: URW 'Base 35' font pack for LaTeX
i hycolor: Implements colour for packages hyperref and bookmark
i hyperref: Extensive support for hypertext in LaTeX
i hyph-utf8: Hyphenation patterns expressed in UTF-8
i hyphen-base: core hyphenation support files
i hyphen-french: French hyphenation patterns.
i ieeetran: Document class for IEEE Transactions journals and conferences
i ifmtarg: If-then-else command for processing potentially empty arguments
i iftex: Am I running under pdfTeX, XeTeX or LuaTeX?
i inconsolata: A monospaced font, with support files for use with TeX
i infwarerr: Complete set of information/warning/error message macros
i intcalc: Expandable arithmetic operations with integers
i kastrup: Convert numbers into binary, octal and hexadecimal
i knuth-lib: Core TeX and Metafont sources from Knuth
i kpathsea: Path searching library for TeX-related files
i kpathsea.windows: windows files of kpathsea
i kpathsea.x86_64-linux: x86_64-linux files of kpathsea
i kvdefinekeys: Define keys for use in the kvsetkeys package
i kvoptions: Key value format for package options
i kvsetkeys: Key value parser with default handler support
i l3backend: LaTeX3 backend drivers
i l3kernel: LaTeX3 programming conventions
i l3packages: High-level LaTeX3 concepts
i lastpage: Reference last page for Page N of M type footers
i latex: A TeX macro package that defines LaTeX
i latex-amsmath-dev: Development pre-release of the LaTeX amsmath bundle
i latex-bin: LaTeX executables and man pages
i latex-bin.windows: windows files of latex-bin
i latex-bin.x86_64-linux: x86_64-linux files of latex-bin
i latex-fonts: A collection of fonts used in LaTeX distributions
i latex-tools-dev: Development pre-release of the LaTeX tools bundle
i latexconfig: configuration files for LaTeX-related formats
i latexmk: Fully automated LaTeX document generation
i latexmk.windows: windows files of latexmk
i latexmk.x86_64-linux: x86_64-linux files of latexmk
i letltxmacro: Let assignment for LaTeX macros
i lipsum: Easy access to the Lorem Ipsum and other dummy texts
i listings: Typeset source code listings using LaTeX
i lm: Latin modern fonts in outline formats
i lm-math: OpenType maths fonts for Latin Modern
i logreq: Support for automation of the LaTeX workflow
i ltxcmds: Some LaTeX kernel commands for general use
i lua-alt-getopt: Process application arguments the same way as getopt_long
i lua-uni-algos: Unicode algorithms for LuaTeX
i luahbtex: LuaTeX with HarfBuzz library for glyph shaping
i luahbtex.windows: windows files of luahbtex
i luahbtex.x86_64-linux: x86_64-linux files of luahbtex
i lualatex-math: Fixes for mathematics-related LuaLaTeX issues
i lualibs: Additional Lua functions for LuaTeX macro programmers
i luaotfload: OpenType 'loader' for Plain TeX and LaTeX
i luaotfload.windows: windows files of luaotfload
i luaotfload.x86_64-linux: x86_64-linux files of luaotfload
i luatex: The LuaTeX engine
i luatex.windows: windows files of luatex
i luatex.x86_64-linux: x86_64-linux files of luatex
i luatexbase: Basic resource management for LuaTeX code
i mdwtools: Miscellaneous tools by Mark Wooding
i metafont: A system for specifying fonts
i metafont.windows: windows files of metafont
i metafont.x86_64-linux: x86_64-linux files of metafont
i mfware: Supporting tools for use with Metafont
i mfware.windows: windows files of mfware
i mfware.x86_64-linux: x86_64-linux files of mfware
i microtype: Subliminal refinements towards typographical perfection
i moderncv: A modern curriculum vitae class
i modes: A collection of Metafont mode_def's
i ms: Various LaTeX packages by Martin Schroder
i multirow: Create tabular cells spanning multiple rows
i mwe: Packages and image files for MWEs
i natbib: Flexible bibliography support
i newtx: Alternative uses of the TX fonts, with improved metrics
i oberdiek: A bundle of packages submitted by Heiko Oberdiek
i pdfescape: Implements pdfTeX's escape features using TeX or e-TeX
i pdftex: A TeX extension for direct creation of PDF
i pdftex.windows: windows files of pdftex
i pdftex.x86_64-linux: x86_64-linux files of pdftex
i pdftexcmds: LuaTeX support for pdfTeX utility functions
i pgf: Create PostScript and PDF graphics in TeX
i pgfgantt: Draw Gantt charts with TikZ
i plain: The Plain TeX format
i preprint: A bundle of packages provided "as is"
i psnfss: Font support for common PostScript fonts
i ragged2e: Alternative versions of "ragged"-type commands
i refcount: Counter operations with label references
i rerunfilecheck: Checksum based rerun checks on auxiliary files
i scheme-infraonly: infrastructure-only scheme (no TeX at all)
i selnolig: Selectively disable typographic ligatures
i setspace: Set space between lines
i siunitx: A comprehensive (SI) units package
i stringenc: Converting a string between different encodings
i sttools: Various macros
i subfig: Figures broken into subfigures
i supertabular: A multi-page tables package
i symbol: URW 'Base 35' font pack for LaTeX
i tex: A sophisticated typesetting engine
i tex-gyre: TeX Fonts extending freely available URW fonts
i tex-ini-files: Model TeX format creation files
i tex.windows: windows files of tex
i tex.x86_64-linux: x86_64-linux files of tex
i texdoc: Documentation access for TeX Live
i texdoc.windows: windows files of texdoc
i texdoc.x86_64-linux: x86_64-linux files of texdoc
i texlive-scripts: TeX Live infrastructure programs
i texlive-scripts.windows: windows files of texlive-scripts
i texlive-scripts.x86_64-linux: x86_64-linux files of texlive-scripts
i texlive.infra: basic TeX Live infrastructure
i texlive.infra.windows: windows files of texlive.infra
i texlive.infra.x86_64-linux: x86_64-linux files of texlive.infra
i texliveonfly: On-the-fly download of missing TeX live packages
i texliveonfly.windows: windows files of texliveonfly
i texliveonfly.x86_64-linux: x86_64-linux files of texliveonfly
i times: URW 'Base 35' font pack for LaTeX
i tipa: Fonts and macros for IPA phonetics characters
i titlesec: Select alternative section titles
i tlgs.windows: Freely available PostScript interpreter
i tlperl.windows: internal Perl for Windows
i todonotes: Marking things to do in a LaTeX document
i tools: The LaTeX standard tools bundle
i translations: Internationalisation of LaTeX2e packages
i translator: Easy translation of strings in LaTeX
i transparent: Using a color stack for transparency with pdfTeX
i unicode-data: Unicode data and loaders for TeX
i unicode-math: Unicode mathematics support for XeTeX and LuaTeX
i uniquecounter: Provides unlimited unique counter
i url: Verbatim with URL-sensitive line breaks
i xcolor: Driver-independent color extensions for LaTeX and pdfLaTeX
i xetex: An extended variant of TeX for use with Unicode sources
i xetex.windows: windows files of xetex
i xetex.x86_64-linux: x86_64-linux files of xetex
i xetexconfig: crop.cfg for XeLaTeX
i xifthen: Extended conditional commands
i xkeyval: Extension of the keyval package
i xstring: String manipulation for (La)TeX
i xunicode: Generate Unicode characters from accented glyphs
i zapfding: URW 'Base 35' font pack for LaTeX
